A Guide to the Sherrill Watkins papers, 1946-2008
Library of Virginia
Library of Virginia
Sherrill Watkins papers, 1946-2008
The Library of Virginia
45486
.35 cubic feet and 1 box
Sherrill Watkins
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
There are no restrictions.
Acquisition Information
Gift of Sherrill Watkins of Midlothian, Virginia
Biographical Information
Sherrill Watkins resides in Midlothian, Virginia.
Scope and Content
Papers, 1946-2008, of Sherrill Watkins of Midlothian, Virginia, consisting of research on the Virginia state flag, including its color, material, display, purchase, and distribution; and containing correspondence, receipts, accounts, photographs, catalogs, drawings, articles, and other material. Also includes information on the appearance of the state seal and coat-of-arms on the flag, as well as information on the United States flag.
Contents List
- Correspondence, 1946, 1949 (Folder 1)
- Correspondence, 1956-1959 (Folder 2)
- Correspondence, 1960-1969 (Folder 3)
- Correspondence, 1970-1979 (Folder 4)
- Correspondence, 1982, 1984, 1986 (Folder 5)
- Correspondence, 1997, 2008 (Folder 6)
- Information on presentation and display of the American flag (Folder 7)
- Information on Virginia state flag (Folder 8)
- Great Seal of Virginia (Folder 9)
- Commonwealth's coat-of-arms (Folder 10)
- Orders and receipts, 1952-1985 (Folder 11)
- Ordering materials, Virginia flag (Folder 12)
- Ordering materials, flags, general (folder 1 of 2) (Folder 13)
- Ordering materials, flags, general (folder 2 of 2) (Folder 14)
- Notes (Folder 15)
- Miscellaneous papers (Folder 16)